(Raj:)Let's hear all
the "Raj is a girl" jokes.
(Howard:)Nope, Bernadette told me
it isn't nice and I'm not allowed.
(Raj:)-Thank you.
-So I won't be making fun of you,
(Howard:)or the things you like, or the fact
that you just want to have fu-un.
(Bernadette:)Howie, stop.
Come on, look at what I'm making.
(Howard:)Oh, that's actually pretty nice.
(Amy:)-I'm making a bracelet.
-Yeah, I'm just making a mess.
(Howard:)You know, instead of beads and glue,
(Howard:)you guys can use my soldering iron.
(Howard:)You'd be able to make
much cooler stuff.
(Raj:)Oh, I think we're doing
just fine, thank you.
(Amy:)Actually, I'd kind of like
to try that.
(Bernadette:)-Me, too.
-Be right back.
(Penny:)When did I have pistachios?
(Sheldon:)Arthur.
(Sheldon:)Door knocker.
That's TV/ money.